gagpress.com 2012-12-27

# Privacy Policy | GAGPress

Privacy Policy

Personal Information  
As with most other websites, we collect the data you provide to us when you visit or post a comment to our site. This information may include your name, your email address, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Chrome, Safari or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. Your personal information will never be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside GAGPress.com.

Cookies  
We also use third party advertisements on GAGPress.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web  
beacons when they advertise on our site. Google, through their Adsense Program, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to GAGPress.com users based on their visit to this and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Third Party Companies

Third party companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).
